connect6.com 2015-05-20

# Connect6° | Privacy Policy

Effective Date: May 15, 2014

We at Connect6, Inc., along with our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, "Connect6°"), respect your concerns about privacy. This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect about our consumers, how we may use the information and with whom we may share it. The notice also describes the measures we take to safeguard the personal information. In addition, we tell you how you can ask us to (i) access or change the personal information we maintain about you, (ii) withdraw consent you previously provided to us, (iii) refrain from sending you certain communications, and (iv) answer questions you may have about our privacy practices

###   
Information We Obtain

We may obtain personal information about Connect6° consumers and users (such as name, contact details and payment information) in connection with various activities such as (i) use of the Connect6° websites and services (ii) publicly-available information about people and companies captured from technology scans of the Internet, (iii) licensed information from other companies, (iv) events in which we participate, and (v) promotions and other offers.

Connect6° creates profiles of business people and companies, which we call "Public Profiles," from different sources. Once Connect6° has collected information about a person or company, Connect6° combines multiple mentions of the same person or company into a Public Profile. The resulting directory of Public Profiles (the "Directory") is then made available to the users of the website and service and Connect6°‘s customers and strategic partners.

The types of personal information we may obtain include:

  * Individual and business contact information (such as name, company name, physical address, email address, and telephone or fax number)
  * Information that enables us to verify your identity
  * Names, email addresses and telephone numbers of others to whom we are asked to send information
  * Username and password to access Connect6° products and services online
  * Social media handles
  * Payment information (including payment card details or online payment services number and billing address) and financial information (such as bank account number)
  * Tax identification number in circumstances in which you request products or services for which this information is required, or in connection with certain promotions or sweepstakes
  * Other personal information that may be provided to us to obtain a Connect6° product or service

Information we may receive from third parties

When you make information publicly available on your social networking page, we may collect that information.

If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to us is covered by this policy. For example, if you access our websites or services through a third-party connection or log-in, for example, through Facebook Connect, by “following,” “liking,” adding the Connect6° application, linking your account to the Connect6° services, etc., that third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to Connect6°. This information could include, but is not limited to, the user ID associated with your account (for example, your Facebook UID), an access token necessary to access that service, any information that you have permitted the third party to share with us including contacts or “Friends,” and any information you have made public in connection with that service. 

In addition, when you visit our websites or use our services, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons. The information we collect in this manner includes IP address, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our site, and dates and times of website visits. A "cookie" is a text file that websites send to a visitor's computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor's browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A "web beacon" also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain "clickstream data," which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored. We may link certain data elements we have collected through automated means, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an email we sent to you. We also may use third-party website analytics tools that collect information about visitor traffic on our websites. Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our websites.

###   
How We Use The Information We Obtain

We may use the information we obtain to:

  * Provide products and services you Process and collect payments
  * Provide customer support and respond to and communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments
  * Establish and manage your Connect6° account (including your online account on connect6.com and its various features, 
  * Offer you products and services we believe may interest you
  * Communicate about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, and other offers or promotions
  * Enable you to post on our blogs and interact with Connect6° through social media
  * Send information to your contacts if you ask us to do so
  * Operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our sales, marketing and advertising; analyzing and enhancing our products, services and websites; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities)
  * Perform data analyses (including market and consumer search, trend analysis, financial analysis, and anonymization of personal information)
  * Protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities
  * Comply with applicable legal requirements and our policies

Connect6° users save time by registering with their favorite social network, since Connect6° can automatically populate new profiles using information gleaned from their existing account. This option is provided to users so they do not have to remember an additional password--when they return to the Connect6°, users can click on their favorite network and sign in using their existing Facebook or LinkedIn credentials. When you use a social networking site or choose to join (or “like”) a Connect6° page on a social network, the social networking site may make some information about you available to Connect6°. Please see the privacy policy for the social networking site to learn more. 

When you use a social networking site to log into Connect6°, you allow us to access to your friends list, your friends’ user IDs, and your connection to those friends. Connect6° may use and store this information to make your experience more social, and shared contacts may also be used to improve Connect6°’s services. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services.

In addition, we use information collected online through cookies, web beacons and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users' visits to our websites and services, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users' interests and the manner in which our users browse our websites and services, and (iii) managing our business. We may supplement data we collect through automated means with information about your location (such as your zip code) to provide you with content that may be of interest to you. We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our websites, identify users of our websites, and gather demographic information about our users. We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our websites, how users navigate through our websites, and how we may tailor our websites to better meet the needs of our users.

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

###   
Interest-Based Advertising

On our websites, we may collect information about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. This section of our Privacy Notice provides details and explains how to exercise your choices.

You may see certain ads on other websites because we participate in advertising networks. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that may be tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad networks may collect includes information about your visits to websites that participate in the relevant advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our websites and on third-party websites that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. 

To learn how to opt out of this ad network interest-based advertising, select [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

###   
Information We Share

We do not sell or otherwise share personal information about you, except as described in this Privacy Notice. We share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.

We also may share the personal information we obtain with our affiliates, franchisees, resellers and joint marketing partners. These entities, which collectively are referred to here as the "Connect6° Business Partners," may use the information for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. We may share physical location data with our Connect6° Business Partners and other third parties to, for example, enhance location-based services and develop accurate and up-to-date maps. In addition, except as described below, unless you object, we may share personal information with third parties who are not Connect6° Business Partners for those parties' own purposes, such as to offer products or services that may interest you.

We also may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation or legal process (such as a court order or subpoena), (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

###   
Your Options

We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you. You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our marketing emails, selecting the Email Unsubscribe link below, adjusting your email preferences in your profile in My Connect6°, or contacting us as specified in the "How To Contact Us" section below. You also may ask us not to send you other marketing communications by contacting us as specified in the "How To Contact Us" section below, and we will honor your request. In addition, as required by law, you may object at any time on legitimate grounds and free of charge to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward.

If you register for a Connect6° account and your information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete your information by logging in with your username and password and making the change. If you would like us to remove information you submitted to Connect6° (i.e., your email address), you can send an email to remove@connect6.com with your request. You may also communicate your request by mail by using the contact information at the end of this Privacy Notice. Once we have received your request, we will act upon the request.

NOTE: Connect6° collects much of its information from the web. Because we search millions of new and old web pages every day, information about you may be acquired again by our service, or contributed by our users, without your knowledge. We recommend that you check back periodically to ensure that your Public Profile contains only the information you choose to have displayed. The best way to avoid having your information found by our search engine (or any other search engine) is to contact the operator of the website that contains the original source(s) of the information and ask for the operator to remove the displayed Information from the web.

[View the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information with certain of our affiliates and other third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as specified below.

###   
Access and Correction

Subject to applicable law, (i) you may obtain a copy of certain personal information we maintain about you or update or correct inaccuracies in that information through your account on connect6.com or (ii) you may have the right to obtain access to personal information we maintain about you by contacting us as indicated in the "How To Contact Us" section of this Privacy Notice. To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we will take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information. In addition, if you believe that personal information we maintain about you is inaccurate, subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request that we correct or amend the information by contacting us as indicated below.

###   
Links To Other Websites

Our websites may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Connect6°. Linked websites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with Connect6°, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.

###   
Data Transfers

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice and in accordance with applicable law.

###   
How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. .

###   
Updates To Our Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post a prominent notice on our websites to notify you of any significant changes to our Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

###   
How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by email at [privacy@connect6.com](mailto:privacy@connect6.com). You also may write to us at:

Connect6°   
Attention: Global Privacy Manager  
27520 Hawthorne Boulevard, Suite 260  
Los Angeles, California 90274  
United States
